<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE xml>
<knimeNode icon="./mapmatcher-16.png" type="Manipulator" xmlns="http://knime.org/node/v2.8" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://knime.org/node/v2.10 http://knime.org/node/v2.10.xsd">
    <name>Map Matcher</name>
    
    <shortDescription>
        Match a route, described as a WKT-like Linestring, to the traversed street segments. 
    </shortDescription>
    
    <fullDescription>
        <intro>This node takes a route, encoded as a WKT Linestring, and matches it to a sequence of traversed OSM road segments, that can be analyzed
        	   by the coverage analyzer nodes in KNOT. 
        	   The node requires that the input table contains three columns:
        	   <ul>
        	   	<li>id, an integer that identifies the owner of the route;</li>
        	   	<li>begin_at, a LocalDateTime that pinpoints the starting time of the route; </li>
        	   	<li>the_geom, a String containing a WKT-like representation of the route.</li>
        	   </ul>
        </intro>
        
        
        <option name="Pair Type">The setting informs the node about the type of coordinate pairs contained in
        the Linestring. Either {lon,lat} or {lon,lat}.</option>
        <option name="Osm Data Path">The path in which the .osm file containing the map data can be found.</option>
        <option name="Osrm Host Field">The url at which the OSRM instance used for map-matching can be reached</option>
        <option name="Include Never Visited Segments">By enabling this checkbox also the segments that were never visited
        will be added to the result table. If not, only the segments visited at least once will show up in the result.</option>
        
    </fullDescription>
    
    <ports>
        <inPort index="0" name="Routes">A table containining data about routes. 
        It must contain the following columns:
        	   <ul>
        	   	<li>id, an integer that identifies the owner of the route;</li>
        	   	<li>begin_at, a LocalDateTime that pinpoints the starting time of the route; </li>
        	   	<li>the_geom, a String containing a WKT-like representation of the route.</li>
        	   </ul> 
       	   </inPort>
        <outPort index="0" name="Matched Segments">A table containing information about the traversed segments
        for each input route and, optionally, data about the segments that were never visited.</outPort>
    </ports>    
</knimeNode>
