<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE xml>
<knimeNode icon="./grid-analyzer-16.png" type="Manipulator" xmlns="http://knime.org/node/v2.8" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://knime.org/node/v2.10 http://knime.org/node/v2.10.xsd">
    <name>Grid Coverage Analyzer</name>
    
    <shortDescription>
        Divide a geographic zone into a grid and see how often each rectangle was visited.
    </shortDescription>
    
    <fullDescription>
        <intro>The node calculate a grid in the specified input zone using the given number of rows
        and columns. It then proceeds to assign each valid entry in the input table to a specific grid cell 
        as a visit. A visit is considered valid if it means a change of rectangle for the route owner, 
        or if the time between the current visit and the previous one was more than the specified number of minutes
        in the input dialog.
        The node offers two output tables, one considering the whole input data-set and the other separating the
        information by day.
        </intro>
        
        <option name="Minimum Latitude">The minimum Latitude of the grid.</option>
	    <option name="Maximum Latitude">The maximum Latitude of the grid.</option>
        <option name="Minimum Longitude">The minimum Longitude of the grid.</option>
		<option name="Minimum Longitude">The minimum Longitude of the grid.</option>
        <option name="Maximum Longitude">The maximum Longitude of the grid.</option>
        <option name="Number of Rows">The number of Rows of the grid.</option>		        
        <option name="Number of columns">The number of Columns of the grid.</option>
        <option name="Minimum time between visits">The number of minutes between to valid visits.</option>
    </fullDescription>
    
    <ports>
        <inPort index="0" name="Route Steps">The input data must contain the following information:
			<ul>
        		<li>owner_id, an integer representing the route step owner.</li>
        		<li>begin_at, a LocalDateTime containing information on the moment at which the route step began.</li>
        		<li>end_at, a LocalDateTime containing information on the moment at which the route step finished</li>
        		<li>the_geom, a String representation of a route formatted as WKT Linestring</li>
        	</ul>
        </inPort>
        <outPort index="0" name="For Day">Information on how often a rectangle was visited broken down by day
        and by time slow within a day.</outPort>
        <outPort index="1" name="For Whole Data Set">Information on how often a rectangle was visited.</outPort>
    </ports>    
   
</knimeNode>
