<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE xml>
<knimeNode icon="./segment-coverage-analysis-16.png" type="Manipulator" xmlns="http://knime.org/node/v2.8" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://knime.org/node/v2.10 http://knime.org/node/v2.10.xsd">
    <name>Segment Coverage Analyzer</name>
    
    <shortDescription>
        This node computes how often and how many times each road segment in the considered OSM map was visited by the input vehicular trajectories.
    </shortDescription>
    
    <fullDescription>
        <intro>The node takes as input a set of map matcher trajectories, possibly computed by the KNOT Map Matcher node. 
        The node computes as coverage metrics both the number of visits for each segment, and the average timegap between subsequent visits.
        </intro>
    </fullDescription>
    
    <ports>
      	<inPort index="0" name="Map-Matched Trajectories">The input table must have the following columns:
        	<ul>
        		<li>an integer representing the vehicle id.</li>
        		<li>a LocalDateTime containing information on the moment at which the traversal of the road segment began.</li>
        		<li>a LocalDateTime containing information on the moment at which the traversal of the road segment ended.</li>
        		<li>origin_id, the OSM id of the origin node of the road segment.</li>
        		<li>destination_id, the OSM id of the destination node of the road segment.</li>
        		<li>tags, the OSM tags associated to the ways to which the origin and destination nodes both belong.</li>
        		<li>a geometry object representing the road segment, encoded as a WKT Linestring</li>
        	</ul>
        		The output of the KNOT Map Matcher node can be directly fed to this node.
        </inPort>
          <outPort index="0" name="Road Segment Coverage Data by Day">A table containing coverage metrics computed for each day in the input dataset. 
          The table contains the following information:
        	<ul>
        		<li>For each road segment, the origin and destination OSM nodes, their tags and a geometry representation as WKT Linestrings.</li>
        		<li>The times it was traversed on a given day, the average time between visits and the same information
        			broken down among four time slots ([00:00-06:00],[06:00-12:00],[12:00-18:00],[18:00-24:00]).</li>
        	</ul>
        </outPort>
	  	<outPort index="1" name="Road Segment Coverage Data">A table containing the following information:
	  		<ul>
	  			<li>For each road segment, the origin and destination OSM nodes, their tags and a geometry representation as WKT Linestrings.</li>
	  			<li>The number of times it was traversed by the input trajectories and the average time between subsequent visits.</li>
	  		</ul>
	  	</outPort>
    </ports>    
</knimeNode>
