<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE xml>
<knimeNode icon="./grid-analyzer-16.png" type="Manipulator" xmlns="http://knime.org/node/v2.8" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://knime.org/node/v2.10 http://knime.org/node/v2.10.xsd">
    <name>Grid Coverage Analyzer</name>
    
    <shortDescription>
        Given a set of map-matched trajectories, splits a geographic area into a grid and computes how often each grid cell is visited.
    </shortDescription>
    
    <fullDescription>
        <intro>The node allows users to define a custom grid over a desidered geographical area by specifying a bounding box, a number of rows
        and a number of columns. It then proceeds to compute the number of times each grid cell was visited by one of the agents performing 
        the input map-matched trajectories. A visit to a grid cell is considered valid if the agent is entering that cell for the first time, 
        or if the time between the current visit and the previous one is more than a threshold (in minutes), which can be customized 
        in the input dialog.
        The node offers two output tables, one considering the whole input data-set and the other grouping the coverage information 
        by day.
        </intro>

        <option name="Min Y">The minimum Latitude of the grid.</option>
	    <option name="Max Y">The maximum Latitude of the grid.</option>
        <option name="Min X">The minimum Longitude of the grid.</option>
        <option name="Max X">The maximum Longitude of the grid.</option>
        <option name="Number of rows">The number of rows of the grid.</option>		        
        <option name="Number of columns">The number of columns of the grid.</option>
        <option name="Minimum time between visits">The minimum number of minutes for two subsequent visits by the same vehicle to be considered distinct.</option>
    </fullDescription>
    
    <ports>
        <inPort index="0" name="Route Steps">The input data must contain the following information:
			<ul>
        		<li>an integer representing the vehicle id.</li>
        		<li>a LocalDateTime containing information on the moment at which the traversal of the road segment began.</li>
        		<li>a LocalDateTime containing information on the moment at which the traversal of the road segment ended.</li>
        		<li>a geometry object representing the road segment, encoded as a WKT Linestring</li>
        	</ul>
        </inPort>
        <outPort index="0" name="Grid Coverage Data By Day">Information on how often a grid cell was visited, broken down by day
        and by time slots within a day.</outPort>
        <outPort index="1" name="Grid Coverage Data">Information on how often a grid cell was visited, aggregate over the entire timespan of the provided data.</outPort>
    </ports>    
   
</knimeNode>
