<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE xml>
<knimeNode icon="./road-route-map-16.png" type="Manipulator" xmlns="http://knime.org/node/v2.8" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://knime.org/node/v2.10 http://knime.org/node/v2.10.xsd">
	<name>Route Calculator</name>

	<shortDescription>
        Computes routes according to different strategies.
    </shortDescription>

	<fullDescription>
		<intro>This Node takes as input a table with the same structure as the "Input data augmented with a Trajectory ID" output of the "Trajectory Partitioner" node and 
		computes vehicular trajectories according to a customizable strategy, producing in output a new set of
        trajectories encoded as WKT Linestrings. The node assumes that the input data contains at least the following information:
        an id of the vehicle, an id of the route, a timestamp, a GPS position.
        The routing computation is done via an external Routing Service. The current implementation supports 
        the Open Source Routing Machine (OSRM) as a routing service. Support for other routing services can be introduced by extending the node.
        As for the routing strategies, currently only "shortest path" is supported.
        This strategy considers only the first and the last points in the original trajectory,
		and computes the shortest path between them. If the original trajectory contains more than two positions,
		the additional positions will be ignored.</intro>

		<option name="Coordinate Input Format"> Either {lon, lat} or {lat, lon}, accordingly to the input format.</option>
		<option name="Routing Service">The routing service to be used. </option>
		<option name="Routing Server endpoint"> Specifies the endpoint for the routing service.</option>
		<option name="Routing Strategy"> Allows the user to select a routing strategy.</option>
		<option name="Minum Duration">Routes that lasts less than this number of minutes will be discarded.</option>
		<option name="Minum Distance">Routes shorter than this number of meters will be discarded.</option>
	</fullDescription>
	<ports>
		<inPort index="0" name="Input data">
			The input table must contains at least the following columns:
			<ul>
				<li>route_id, a long identifying the route.</li>
				<li>vehicle_id, an integer identifying the vehicle id;</li>
				<li>timestamp, a String identifying when this position was recorded;</li>
				<li>location, a WKT String containing positions (e.g.: "POINT( coordinate1 coordinate2)".</li>
			</ul>
			The input data must be sorted by route_id.
		</inPort>
		<outPort index="0" name="Computed routes">This port contains the routes computed according to the selected
		routing strategy.</outPort>
	</ports>
</knimeNode>
