<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Contributors on</title><link>https://luistar.github.io/knot/contributors/</link><description>Recent content in Contributors on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:50:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://luistar.github.io/knot/contributors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sergio Di Martino</title><link>https://luistar.github.io/knot/contributors/sergio-di-martino/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2020 08:50:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://luistar.github.io/knot/contributors/sergio-di-martino/</guid><description>Sergio is Associate Professor at the Department of Electrical Engineering and Information Technology of the University of Naples Federico II, Italy, where he is also the co-chair of the Knowledge Management and Engineering (Knome) Lab. His research interests focus on knowledge discovery and exploitation from complex spatio-temporal datasets, especially in the field of mobility. He supervises and coordinates the KNOT project.</description></item><item><title>Luigi Libero Lucio Starace</title><link>https://luistar.github.io/knot/contributors/luigi-libero-lucio-starace/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:50:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://luistar.github.io/knot/contributors/luigi-libero-lucio-starace/</guid><description>Luigi is a Ph.D. student in Information Technology and Electrical Engineering at the University of Naples Federico II, Italy. His research interests include software engineering, design and evaluation of end-to-end testing techniques, formal methods, and applications of computer science to intelligent transportation systems and smart cities. He supervises and coordinates students working on the KNOT project, and is responsible for this website.</description></item><item><title>Sinogrante Matteo Principe</title><link>https://luistar.github.io/knot/contributors/sinogrante-matteo-principe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 08:50:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://luistar.github.io/knot/contributors/sinogrante-matteo-principe/</guid><description>As part a curricular internship for the B.Sc. degree in Computer Science, Sinogrante (friends can call him Sino!) developed the Trajectory Partitioner, the Map Matcher, the Trajectory Manipulator and the Segment and Grid Coverage Analyzer nodes.</description></item></channel></rss>