<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Contributors on</title><link>https://luistar.github.io/knot/contributors/</link><description>Recent content in Contributors on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:50:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://luistar.github.io/knot/contributors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sergio Di Martino</title><link>https://luistar.github.io/knot/contributors/sergio-di-martino/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2020 08:50:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://luistar.github.io/knot/contributors/sergio-di-martino/</guid><description>Sergio is an Associate Professor at the Department of Electrical Engineering and Information Technology of the University of Naples Federico II, Italy, where he is also the co-chair of the Knowledge Management and Engineering (KnoME) Lab. His research interests focus on knowledge discovery and exploitation from complex spatio-temporal datasets, especially in the field of mobility. He supervises and coordinates the KNOT project.</description></item><item><title>Luigi Libero Lucio Starace</title><link>https://luistar.github.io/knot/contributors/luigi-libero-lucio-starace/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:50:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://luistar.github.io/knot/contributors/luigi-libero-lucio-starace/</guid><description>Luigi (personal website here) is a Ph.D. student at the Università degli Studi di Napoli Federico II, Italy. His research interests include software engineering, design and evaluation of end-to-end testing techniques, formal methods, and applications of computer science to intelligent transportation systems and smart cities. He supervises and coordinates students working on the KNOT project, and is responsible for this website.</description></item><item><title>Franca Rocco di Torrepadula</title><link>https://luistar.github.io/knot/contributors/franca-rocco-di-torrepadula/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 08:50:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://luistar.github.io/knot/contributors/franca-rocco-di-torrepadula/</guid><description>Franca is a Ph.D. student at the Università degli Studi di Napoli Federico II, in Italy. Her research is focused on the use of the Internet of Things and Machine Learning Techniques in the context of Industry 4.0 and Intelligent Transportation Systems. She used KNOT in many of her research activities, and contributed to the design and testing of several components.</description></item><item><title>Sinogrante Matteo Principe</title><link>https://luistar.github.io/knot/contributors/sinogrante-matteo-principe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 08:50:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://luistar.github.io/knot/contributors/sinogrante-matteo-principe/</guid><description>As part of a curricular internship for the B.Sc. degree in Computer Science, Sinogrante (friends can call him Sino!) developed the Trajectory Partitioner, the Map Matcher, the Trajectory Manipulator and the Segment and Grid Coverage Analyzer nodes.</description></item><item><title>Roland Varriale</title><link>https://luistar.github.io/knot/contributors/roland-varriale/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 08:50:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://luistar.github.io/knot/contributors/roland-varriale/</guid><description>As part of a curricular internship for the B.Sc. degree in Computer Science, Roland worked on a major update for the KNOT nodes, featuring usability improvements including column selection and graphical bounding-box selection in the configuration dialogs. Moreover, Roland developed the new Bounding Box Filter node, and worked on preparing KNOT for deployment on the official KNIME Hub.</description></item></channel></rss>